Wow, Hyesung
This place is too fancy
It's the least I can do
to repay your help
Oh, it's delicious
- It starts on the 17th?
- Yes
I'll be an assistant
director in the drama
- Really?
- Yeah
I was urgently put in
as a replacement
Hey, I'm so glad
to work with you
[Shindecent]
What are you doing?
Is that Shin Yoo-il?
How did you know that?
I can tell
from your face
But
I guess you better keep
some distance from him
Why?
Because of
those rumors?
Everyone knows
he's indecent
but other than that…
Why take a risk
for nothing?
Well, he doesn't look
like that bad person
I heard he has dozens
of sex partners
He even got sponsored
That's what people
in this industry say
Are you sure
that's all true?
Even someone like you
heard those rumors
What do you think?
He's done whatever
it takes for success
He's also using you now
I need
a cigarette break